meetlima.com 2015-09-23

# Lima - A World Where Your Devices Act As One

_Last Modified: May 26, 2014_

## Introduction

Lima Technology Inc, a Delaware Corporation ( “we” “us” or “Lima”), the makers of Lima (the “Product”) respects your privacy and are committed to protecting it through compliance with this policy.

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website www.meetlima.com (our “Website”) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information. Please read this policy carefully. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see Changes to our Privacy Policy). Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates. Contact us at privacy@meetlima.com if you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy.

## Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It

Lima collects the following types of information from users of the Website: (1) Personal Data and (2) Web Tracking Data.

 **Personal Data includes:**

The information that is personally identifiable to you and that you voluntarily give us when you use the Website to purchase or reserve a Product. The information you provide us via email or other communications with us. When providing us this data you are giving us permission to use this data per the terms of this policy. This information includes but is not limited to, your email, name, address etc. Please note that all payments are processed via third party payment processors, Lima does not store any of your credit card information. Please be careful not to provide any personal information on any public sections of the Website.

 **Web Tracking Data includes:**

Data that Lima and its third-party service providers may collect using web tracking technologies, such as cookies, web beacons, pixel tags and clear GIFs, related to your usage of the Website. Such data may include the address of the websites you visited before and after you visited the Website, the type of browser you are using, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, what pages of the Website you visit and what links you clicked on. In order to collect Web Tracking Data and to make your use of the Website more efficient, we may store cookies on your computer. Cookies are small files that contain a string of alphanumeric characters that are placed on your device/computer from websites, often times used to facilitate a more pleasant user experience. A session cookie is one that exists for the time period that your browser is open. A persistent cookie is one that is saved on your device/computer even after the browser is closed. You are able to refuse cookies by changing settings in your browser. Please refer to “Help” in your browser for specific instructions. Like many websites, we may use both session cookies and persistent cookies.

## Information Usage

 **Personal Data:**  We will use and store Personal Data to deliver the Product to you, and to improve the Product and Website, and for internal operational and administrative purposes.

 **Web Tracking Data:**  We use Web Tracking Data to administer the Website and to develop aggregate, statistical information on usage of the Services. This allows us to determine which features visitors like best, personalize your user experience, and measure overall effectiveness.

 **Aggregate Data:**  We will also use Personal Data and Web Tracking Data to create aggregated data for analytical purposes. This aggregated data does not contain personally identifiable information and is used to understand our customer base and to better serve our market. This data may also be used by our service providers, partners, or affiliates.

 **Email Communications:**  If you create an account and provide your email address, we may send you administrative and promotional emails. If you wish to opt out of promotional emails, you may do so by following the “unsubscribe” instructions in the email.

## Information Disclosure

 **Personal Data:**  Lima does not sell or rent Personal Data, and we will not disclose your email address to any third party for marketing purposes. We will disclose your Personal Data to third parties only in the following limited circumstances:

(i) to third-party contractors and partners engaged to provide services on behalf of Lima (“Contractors”) who are performing marketing services, delivering goods or services, administering promotions, analyzing data and usage of the Products, processing payments, operating the website or products or providing support and maintenance services for the Products. We use reasonable efforts to enter into agreements with all Contractors that require Contractors to use the Personal Information they receive only to perform services for us; and

(ii) when we have your consent to share the information.

 **Web Tracking Data:**  We disclose Web Tracking Data to third party advertisers and advertising agencies, merchants, and Contractors, in order for Lima and such third parties to analyze the behaviour of users, to operate and improve the Product, and to target advertising to users. We may also publish this information in order to promote Lima and the Product.

As you browse www.meetlima.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, Adroll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with www.meetlima.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can visit[ this page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to opt out of Adroll's and their partners' targeted advertising. 

 **Aggregate Information:**  We may disclose anonymous, aggregated information to third parties such as potential business partners, merchants, advertisers, and funding sources, in order to describe our business and operations.

 **Network Operators:**  Use of the Website may involve use of the services of third-party telecommunications carriers and service providers (such as the services of the carrier that provides cellphone and internet service to you). Such carriers and service providers are not Lima Contractors, and any information that a carrier collects in connection with your use of the Service is not “Personal Data” and is not subject to this Privacy Policy. Lima is not responsible for the acts or omissions of telecommunications carriers or service providers.

 **Additional Disclosures:**  Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Privacy Policy, Lima reserves the right to use or disclose Personal Data and any other information we collect in connection with the Website (a) to any successor to Lima’s business, including as a result of any merger, acquisition, asset sale or similar transaction, (b) to any law enforcement, judicial authority, or governmental or regulatory authority, to the extent required by law or legal process, or (c) if in Lima’s reasonable discretion, such use or disclosure is necessary to enforce or protect Lima’s legal rights or to protect third parties.

## General Terms

### Children

Lima does not knowingly collect or retain personally identifiable information about persons under 13 years of age. Any person who provides their personal information to Lima via the Website represents that they are 13 years of age or older. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor the activity of those under 13 years of age. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided personally identifiable data to Lima, please contact us, and we will make every effort to delete that information from our databases.

### Data Security

Lima stores data in databases in the US and abroad. The third-party analytics service providers and data centres we work with, use commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of all data. Although these third-parties take measures to provide data security, this is no guarantee that the data may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by a breach of their systems. Because no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, we cannot ensure the security of the data you transmit using the Website, and you do so at your own risk.

### Privacy Settings/Opt Out/Changes

If you would like your Personal Data permanently removed from our database or changed, please contact us at privacy@meetlima.com. We will promptly delete your account and you will no longer receive email from Lima. Your removal from the mailing list or database will not remove records of past transactions or delete information stored in our data backups and archives. Data on past transactions and data stored in backups and archives will be deleted in the normal course of Lima's business.

### Links

The Website may contain links to other websites. Lima is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those websites. Users should be aware of this when they leave our website, and review the privacy statements of each third party website. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Website.

### Website Visitors from outside the United States

Lima and its servers are located in the United States and France and are subject to the applicable state and federal laws of the United States and France. If you choose to access or use the Services, you consent to the use and disclosure of information in accordance with this privacy policy and subject to such laws.

## Contact

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please send us an email at privacy@meetlima.com.
